黑帮医生 前情提要
Previously on The Mob Doctor
只要你还在芝加哥，你就欠我的
As long as you are in Chicago I own you,
一言为定
that's the deal.
郊区应该归我们管
Downtown should be ours.
我们在创造历史，最好别站错队伍
We're about to make history here.Better be on the right side of it.
郊区太抢眼了
Downtown is too high-profile.
我说了，我不感兴趣
Like I said, I ain't interested.
你想知道什么？
What do you want to know?
是不是你杀了我爸爸？
Did you kill my dad?
我跟你发誓
I swear to you,
以我的性命和你妈的性命发誓
on my life,on your mother's life,
我没杀你爸爸
I did not kill your father.
关于那天晚上你都知道些什么？
You know something? At the end of the day,
我和老康
me and Constantine...
首先我们都是父亲
we're fathers first.
老康还有个孩子？
Constantine has kids?
你谁呀？
Who the hell is this guy?
好久不见了
It's been a long time.
我对人脸有过目不忘的能耐
I never forget a face.
你走近点好好看看
Then look closer.
是我呀，爸爸
It's me, Dad.
见到你真好，卢克
It's good to see you, Luke.
我在监狱里的时候听说你妈妈去世了
I heard about your mom's passing when I was in the joint.
我非常的抱歉
I'm very sorry.
是吗？我猜你的吊唁卡一定让邮局给弄丢了
Yeah? I guess your condolence card was lost in the mail.
我们都25年没见面了
Well... we haven't seen each other in 25 years.
你需要什么？
What do you need?
哦，我惹了个麻烦
Um, I'm in trouble.
我就说么
That I figured.
我的不动产大部分都在
I'm in real estate down in Miami...
迈阿密的南部海滩
South Beach, mostly.
我想我应该在房市低迷的时候购入
I figured I should go big while the rates were low...
你知道，获取有利条件
You know, take advantage.
有雄心，这是好事
Ambitious...that's a good thing.
我在海边买了块地
I got my hands on a beachfront property...
能容纳十套房子那么大
Big enough I could put up 10 units.
一开始经营得还不错
And it was all going great
结果我栽在了经营许可证上
until I got screwed on the permits,
银行不肯贷款给我
and then the banks wouldn't even look at me.
让我猜猜，有人给你提供了私人贷款
Let me guess... somebody offered you a private loan.
人家当时很绝望么
I was desperate,
我本来有三个月的时间偿还贷款
and I was supposed to have three months to pay them back.
这是老把戏了
That's the oldest trick in the book.
这帮人等你把钱花完之后
They wait for you to spend the money.
再把利率抬高
And then they call in the loan at high interest.
他们把我的帐全都转到
It turns out the money I borrowed
诺格拉斯·卡特尔那里
belongs to the Nogales Cartel.
是啊，孩子，你说的对
Yeah, well...you're right, kid.
你确实惹了大麻烦
You're in a lot of trouble.
他们闯入我家
They broke into my house.
我不知道该怎么办，只能跑出来了
I-I didn't know what to do.I just ran.
行了，你想让我帮你调查这个事是吧
All right,you let me look into it.
在这段时间里，你就住在我家吧
In the meantime, why don't you stay at my house?
你会比较安全
You'll be safer.
直说了吧，我不是来寻亲来的
All due respect, I'm not looking for a father.
我只是想寻求帮助
I'm just looking for help.
我明白
I understand.
卢克
Luke.
我明天再跟你联系
I'll check back with you tomorrow.
自己小心点
Well, be careful.
他真是你儿子吗？
He's really your kid, huh?
是的，他惹上诺格拉斯·卡特尔
Yeah. He's in the weeds with the Nogales Cartel.
我得保护他
I want him protected.
看着他，吉尔，别让他走出你的视线
Stay with him, Gio.Don't let him out of your sight.
提诺，诺格拉斯·卡特尔……
Tino, the Nogales Cartel...
你知道这会带来麻烦对吗？
You know this could be a problem, right?
他是我的儿子，斯塔沃斯，我能不管吗？
He's my blood, stavos.What can I do?
跟特拉帕尼说一声，我要见他
Tell Trapani I want a meeting.
这些孕妇都怎么回事啊？
What's with all the pregnant people?
有个人在楼上的心里助产室晕倒了
Guy collapsed in a Lamaze class upstairs.
我们是创伤科的，我是沃尔克克斯大夫
We're from the trauma team.I'm Dr. Wilcox.
这是德芙琳大夫
This is Dr. Devlin.
我，我是贝瑟尼
I-I'm Bethany.
这是我丈夫斯图尔特
This... this is Stuart,my husband.
我们正在学习婴儿心肺复苏术，他突然就晕过去了
We were just learning baby CPR,and he just passed out.
血压83,40，可能是血管迷走神经性晕厥
Pressure's 83/40.Probably vasovagal.
输液一公升。他有什么慢性病吗？
Hang a liter.Any chronic illnesses?
没有。一般都吃什么药？
- No.- Medications?
没有，什么都不吃
No, nothing.
我们遵循自然生育
We're... we're having a natural pregnancy.
嗯，我们俩都是
Um, yeah, well, both of us.
波形宽而多变，像是室性心动过速
Looks like a wide-complex tachycardia, maybe v-tach.
这可能就是晕倒的原因
Well, that would explain the fainting.
注射胺碘酮
Start an amio drip.
心脏收缩降到68了，我们的赶紧注射胺碘酮
Systolic's down to 68.We need that amio fast!
不，别用那个了，他太不稳定了
No, forget it.He's too unstable.
我觉得得给他用心电复律器
I think we should cardiovert him.
打依托咪酯
Push the etomidate.
好吧，听着，贝瑟尼
All right, listen, Bethany.
我们得给他进行电击治疗
We're just gonna give him a small electrical shock
让他的心率恢复正常
to reset his heart to a normal rhythm, okay?
让护士带你到外边等着好吗？
Would you go with the nurse,wait outside?
我们会尽快告诉你结果的
We'll come talk to you as soon as we can.
不，我……
No. I...
准备，走你
- Paddles.- Clear.
安培表无显示
Amp of epi.
加油
Come on.
别死啊
提诺，你把我约到这儿来
Tino, you brought me all the way out here.
也没给我带点吃的
You don't even bring those pignoli biscotti.
是啊，要是再吃那些垃圾食品
Yeah, you keep eating crap like that,
就等着等着让人把你
it's gonna take a dozen pallbearers
抬进坟墓吧
to put you in the ground, huh?
生意怎么样
How's business?
没法说，你叫我来干吗？
Can't complain. So?
听说你跟诺格拉斯·卡特尔有合作关系
Word is, you're in bed with the Nogales Cartel.
我给了他们一个废车处理的生意
I gave them a deal to traffic junk on the Eisenhower,
你说的是这个吗？
if that's what you mean.Why?
我有个很亲密的人跟他们有麻烦了
I got a guy close to me.He's underwater with them.
我想让你给他们打个电话
I'd like you to make a phone call,
帮我把他约出来单独见个面
arrange a sit-down for me.
你帮这个人是谁？
Who's the guy?
我儿子
My son.
啊，是你跟黑泽·克拉斯特（伊利诺伊州城市）那个女的生的孩子吧
Ah, the kid you had with that broad from Hazel Crest.
对，听着，我很感激你能帮我这个忙
Yeah. Look, I appreciate you doing me this favor.
没问题，我会尽力帮你的
No problem. I'll...I'll do the best I can.
你告诉他们我会负责他们全部的损失
You tell them I'll cover everything.
哦
Ah.
啊
怎么了？
Is something wrong?
啊，我的妞
Ah, it's my girl.
她得了一种奇怪的感冒，好几个礼拜都没好
She's got some weird flu kicking her ass the past few weeks.
病得都下不来床
She can barely get out of bed.
哦，你知道我手下有个能出诊的大夫
Yeah, well, you know I got a doctor who makes house calls.
你想让我叫她帮着看看吗？
You want me to bring her over?
真的？
Really?
我的意思是，咱们互相帮助，朋友不就是这样嘛
I mean, that's how it works, huh? You help me. I help you.
我不该那么着急给他做心率复苏
I shouldn't have rushed into the cardioversion.
我们应该等胺碘酮或者试试腺苷（都是药）
We should have waited for amio or... or tried adenosine.
如果他的体征不稳定
And that could have sent him straight into v-fib
就是直接导致他的心律失常
if he wasn't going there already.
格蕾丝，处理心动过速的首要原则是
First rule of wide-complex tachycardia, Grace...
不能有创伤
Do no harm.
我错了
This is my fault.
你怎么跟他妻子解释？
What are we gonna say to his wife?
我们做了个病理判断
We made a judgment call,
我们俩都认为那是正确的处理方法
and we both thought it was the right one.
斯图尔特怎么样了？
How's Stuart?
咱们坐下说吧
Will you sit down?
马斯蓝夫人，非常抱歉
Mrs. Maslan,I am so sorry.
你丈夫死了
Your husband died.
噢，我的天啊
Oh, my God.
我想看看他
I want to see him.
他尸骨未寒
He's still warm.
我们给他做了心脏起搏，但是他没挺过来
We tried to restart his heart,but he didn't respond.
你们为什么不给他抢救？
Why couldn't you help him?
我们已经尽力了
We tried everything we could.
斯图尔特的心率严重失常
Stuart had a severely unstable heart rhythm.
一旦发作，谁也没办法挽救
Sometimes when that happens,you just can't restore it.
要不要我给你的家人打电话？
Is there anyone that we can call?
我在哪？
Where am I?
黑帮天使 第一季 第十二集 复活
The Mob Doctor 01x12 Resurrection
==中文翻译：@godort==
我听说你们今天早上很兴奋
I hear you folks had quite an exciting morning.
上一分钟我还在心里助产室，一转眼我就死了
One minute we were at Lamaze,and then apparently I died.
抱歉
Excuse me.
没有心肌梗塞的征兆
No evidence of infarction.
醒来之后，他就一点事儿都没有了
Other than this cold,he's been perfectly healthy.
哦，太神奇了
Oh, he is. Or was.
到底怎么回事？
How did this happen?
有些医学论文上
There are several cases in the medical literature
把这种现象叫做“拉萨路综合征”
of what's called "Lazarus Syndrome."
病人在经过抢救无效宣布死亡之后
People pronounced dead who come back to life
又活过来了
after attempts at resuscitation have failed.
这种情况非常罕见
It's extremely rare.
我当了三十年医生了，从来没见过这种情况
In 30 years of practice,I've never seen a case,
所以我想跟我的两位大夫谈谈
which is why I'd like to borrow my two doctors for a moment,
如果你不介意的话。不，当然不介意
- if you don't mind.- No, of course.
说说吧，到底怎么回事？
So, what exactly happened in there?
我们也不知道
We have no idea.
你们是通过什么判定他死亡的？
What criteria did you use to call the code?
30分钟以上心脏没有跳动
Over 30 minutes in asystole,
瞳孔放大而且没反应
pupils fixed and dilated,
超声波显示心脏无跳动
and no cardiac activity on ultrasound.
嗯，好吧，那就说们确实死了
Mm, well, that does sound pretty dead.
他的心率仍然很不稳定
His rhythm is still grossly unstable.
但是没有心脏缺血病状
But no evidence of ischemia.
我们还是想不明白为什么他的心脏停了那么长时间又开始跳了
We still can't figure out why his heart stopped or restarted.
好吧，去约一下冠状动脉血栓CT检查
All right, order a stat coronary C.T. and echo,
确保他别再死过去
and make sure our Lazarus doesn't return to the cave.
好，我这就去
Answer it. I got this.
听着，格蕾丝，我们要去看的这个人
Listen, Grace,the guy we're gonna go see...
是我的一个老朋友
He's been a friend of mine a long time.
他可能会跟你提到什么事
And he might mention something to you
我宁愿先告诉你
that I'd rather you hear from me.
我有一个儿子
I have a son.
他叫卢克
His name is Luke.
今天是我25年来第一次见到他
And I saw him today for the first time in 25 years.
你们的关系不是那么亲密啊
Not exactly close, huh?
我爱我的儿子
I love my son,
我曾经尝试着关心他和他母亲
and I tried to do right by him and his mom.
然而我想他的母亲已经厌倦了这种生活
And I guess she just got tired of the life
他们搬到佛罗里达去了
and took off for Florida.
她让我发誓远离我们的儿子
She made me promise to stay away from him.
这对我来说太痛苦了
And I can't tell you how hard that was...
你知道，每个生日，每个节日
you know, birthdays, holidays,
连个电话都没有
not to pick up the phone.
但是我守住了我的诺言
But I kept my word.
你想弥补你们的父子关系？
You gonna try and reconnect?
不，太晚了
No, it's too late.
他只想让我把他从火坑里拉出来
He just wants me to dig him out of a jam.
除非你死了，否则没有什么晚不晚的
It's never too late till you're dead.
你又成乐天派了
Look who's the optimist.
如果这对你来说很重要，那么对他也一样
Just means if it matters to you, it might matter to him.
欢迎之至，提诺
Welcome, Tino.
这是特拉帕尼先生，这是德芙琳大夫
Mr. Trapani,this is Dr. Devlin.
嘿，叫我艾尔就行了，你能来真是太好了
Hi. I'm Al.Thanks for coming.
谁病了？
Where's your patient?
让大夫去克洛伊的房间
Take the doc up to Chloe's room.
我一会就来
I'll be right there.
我给卡特尔捎信过去了
I floated the message to the cartel
我跟他说你愿意把卢克的欠款全部还清
that you're willing to pay off Luke's debt.
他说什么呀？
And?
这可是在跟大人物打交道啊
It's working its way up the food chain.
你好像有事瞒着我，艾尔
There's something you're not telling me, Al.
他们已经采取惩罚性措施了
They've already taken punitive measures.
他们要对卢克进行报复行动
They've ordered a hit on Luke.
杀手已经到芝加哥了
The guy they hired is boots down in Chicago.
这人叫迪亚哥·布里特
It's Diego Balt.
他从未失手过，提诺
He never misses, Tino.
你的意思是说已经太晚了吗？
Are you saying it's too late?
我发誓我已经尽力帮你了
I'll do the best I can...I give you my word.
巴闭，给吉尔打电话
Bobby, call Gio.
告诉他找到卢克，我们随后就来
Tell him to find Luke,that we're on our way.
这就去
I'm on it.
我会把格蕾丝送回去的
I'll send a car for Grace.
哦，没发炎
Well, got no redness.
太好了
That's something.
甲状腺正常
Glands feel normal.
我浑身都疼
I just hurt all over.
你不发烧
Well, your temperature is fine.
哦，她得什么病了，大夫
So, um, what's wrong with her, doc...
是重感冒之类的吗？
Some kind of bad flu or something?
我还不敢肯定
I'm not really sure yet.
有什么慢性病或者做过什么手术吗？
Any chronic medical issues or surgeries?
我做过一两个整形手术
Well, I may have had a thing or two done
为了让我跳舞的时候更好看
to improve my looks back when I was dancing...
你知道的，很普通的那种
you know, normal stuff.
那么，都是什么样的手术？
So, what kind of surgeries are we talking about?
哦，鼻子，腹部，当然还有隆胸
Uh, nose, tummy,the girls, of course.
那么，你植入的是硅胶还是盐溶液？
And, um, your implants...Are they silicone or saline?
哦，我不知道
Uh... I don't know.
那是我的一个常客送我的圣诞礼物
They were a Christmas present to me from one of my regulars.
不能对礼物太挑剔对吗？
Don't look a gift horse in the mouth, right?
问这干吗？
Why?
硅胶泄露
Silicone leaks...
会导致肌肉疼痛和免疫失调
They can cause fibromyalgia or immune disorders.
你能让我看看吗？
Do you mind if I check?
半个芝加哥的人都看过我的胸部，看吧
Half of Chicago's seen my boobs,so knock yourself out.
好吧
All right.
好
Okay.
右边这个比左边的小
The right one's smaller than the left.
这样正常吗？不正常
- Has it always been that way? - No.
咱们得把它取出来再做一些化验
We're gonna need to remove them and run some tests.
越快越好。哦，我不确定
- The sooner the better.- Uh, I don't know.
嘿，嘿，嘿，听我说，不用担心
Hey, hey, hey. Look at me.It's nothing to worry about.
你得先把你的病治好
We got to fix whatever's making you sick.
好吧
Okay.
我给医院打个电话定一间手术室
I'll call the hospital and book an O.R.
我马上就到，头儿
You almost here, boss?
他在富兰克林大街往北走了
He's heading north on Franklin.
他刚走过路口
He just passed superior.
不用，我能盯住他
No, I got him.
行吧
All right.
好，从芝加哥和富人区中间的小道传过去
All right, come up through the alley between Chicago
我能接到他，好吧？
and Superior...I'm gonna grab him, all right?
好吧，我看见他了。
All right. I got him.All right.
卢克，卢克！
Luke. Luke!
你在这干吗？
What are you doing here?
你爸爸叫我来找你。我不需要保姆
Your father sent me.I don't need a babysitter.
嘿，哥们，我只是执行命令，好吗？
Hey, buddy, I just do as I'm told, all right?
赶紧进来，你差点把我屎吓出来
Get in. You scared the crap out of me.
你被陷害了，孩子。你什么意思？
You been made, kid. What are you talking about?
你还带着你从迈阿密带过来的手机呢吧？
Did you bring your cellphone from Miami?
我当然带着了。让我看看
Of course I did.Let me see it.
嘿！你想被杀死吗？
Hey! You want to get killed?
你刚才就差点让人杀了
Because that's almost what just happened.
追你的这个人是个职业杀手
This guy who's after you is a serious player.
现在我得把你送到一个安全的地方
Now I got to get you someplace safe.
你是说这个事你搞不定吗？
Are you telling me you can't make this go away?
你要是恨我，我也没意见
You want to hate me, I'll learn to live with that.
但是你要想从这件事里全身而退
But if you're gonna get through this,
你就必须得照我说的做
you're gonna do exactly what I tell you.
艾尔哪去了
Where's Al.
他在走廊上呢
He's just down the hall.
嘿，克洛伊，我是鲁滨逊大夫
Hi, Chloe.I'm Dr. Robinson.
我来接管你
I'm gonna be scrubbing in.
必须得做这个手术吗？
Are you sure we have to do this?
我的意思是，会不会什么地方搞错了？
I mean, what if something goes wrong?
如果你体内的硅胶泄露了
Well, if you have a silicone leak,
我们就必须把它取出来
we have to take care of it.
德芙琳大夫说得对，不过别担心
Dr. Devlin's right.But don't worry...
不会有事的
We're not gonna let anything happen to you.
好吧
Okay.
开始吧
Let's do it.
静脉注射管插进去了
I.V. Line is in.
咱们确保我做完手术之后
Just make sure that the new girls
还能让艾尔喜欢我，好吗？
are up to Al's standards, okay?
绝对没问题
Absolutely.
那么，你看这个健康的心脏模型中
So, you can see in this model of a healthy heart
电流通过的
how the electrical current flows
的正确途径
in a regular pattern down well-defined pathways.
模型显示，斯图尔特的心脏
In this model, Stuart's heart,
电流脉冲
the contractions and electrical impulses
是杂乱无序的
are erratic and disorganized.
他两周没睡觉了
He hasn't slept in two weeks.
我以为是太兴奋了呢
I thought it was the excitement.
失眠？老做噩梦
- Insomnia? - Nightmares.
我老能梦见我抱着我儿子
I-I keep dreaming that I'm holding our son
然后把他扔到喷泉的池子里去
and I drop him down a well.
我们家根本就没有喷泉
We...We don't have a well.
我甚至都没见过喷泉，这真可耻
I've never even seen a well.It's... it's pitiful.
哦，不，这没什么
Oh, no, not at all.
第一次当爸爸都会很恐慌的
Becoming a father for the first time can be pretty terrifying.
那么，没准这就是问题所在，他反复说孩子的事
So, maybe that's what it is... He's stressed out over the baby.
我不同意，马斯蓝夫人
I don't think so,Mrs. Maslan.
可能是斯图尔特的生物电途径枯竭了
It's as if Stuart's electrical pathways are dying,
而我们暂时还查不出来原因
and our tests haven't been able to pinpoint why.
也就是说他还会再死一次？
So he could die again?
在我们找到病因之前
Until we understand the etiology,
这都不好说的
that's hard to predict.
好吧，那就是说
All right, so it looks like
我们还得在这呆一阵了
we're gonna be here for a little while.
预约EP检查，给他换抗肾上腺素药
Order an E.P. study and switch him to sotalol.
好的
Yes, sir.
你不是喜欢挑战么，威尔科克斯大夫
You like a challenge,Dr. wilcox.
挑战来了
Looks like you've got one.
这怎么可能呐？
How is this possible?
我还以为克洛伊的症状是来自硅胶泄露呢
I thought Chloe's symptoms were from a silicone leak.
但，那绝对是盐溶液
Well, those are definitely saline.
是啊
Yeah.
听着，好消息是
Look, good news...
她需要重新把假胸放回去
She needed the implants replaced,
而且我觉得我们干得不错
and I think we did an excellent job.
听着，她可能感染了某种病毒
Look, she probably just has a virus or something.
他不发烧
She didn't have a fever.
她也没有什么好转
Her symptoms aren't improving.
咱们肯定漏掉了什么
We're missing something.
大夫，她流血了
Doctors, she's bleeding.
是伤口吗？
From the incision site?
她的尿路大出血
Her urinary tract is hemorrhaging.
好吧，把她推到重症监护室去
Okay, get her to the ICU for monitoring.
给她做一个尿路造影照片
Type and cross for four and get a stat urogram.
赶快
Come on. Let's go.
好吧
All right.
这有足够你吃上几天的食物
You got enough food for a few days.
从现在开始，在我告诉你没事了之前，不要离开这间房间
Now, don't leave the room until you get the okay from me.
这太可怕了
This is crazy.
要不然我报警吧
Maybe I should have just called the cops.
不行，那是你最不应该做的事
No, that's the last thing you should have done.
你就在这安顿好就行了
Just settle down.
帕拉特尼正在跟他们接洽
Trapani's working his connections.
在这期间，我会让斯塔沃斯
In the meantime, I got Stavos reaching out
到迈阿密去找卡提尔的律师
to one of the cartel's top lawyers in Miami.
放心吧，都会搞定的，孩子
Everything's gonna be fine, kid.
你怎么那么淡定呢？他们已经找到过我了！
How can you say that? They already found me once!
除非你自己干出什么蠢事，否则不会有人找到你的
Nobody's gonna find you unless you do something stupid,
而且你也不会干蠢事的对吧
and you're not gonna do that.
哥们，别紧张，我们有人在这儿监视
Buddy, relax.We'll watch a little something.
不会有事的
We'll eat a little something.It'll be good.
你要不要我在门外安排点保安？
You want me to put a couple guys outside?
不用了，越低调行事约不显眼。
No. The lower the profile,the better.
艾尔，你的妞怎么样了？
Al, how's your broad?
她没事
She's okay.
她得了什么并发症
She had some kind of complication.
他们正在给她做检查
They're doing a scan now.
那些医生都很专业的
Well, she's in good hands.
谢谢
Thanks.
哦，咱们的对手有消息了
So, uh, I heard back from our compadres.
什么消息？
So, what's the deal?
我们能不能把那些债权都买下来？
Can we buy out of this with a bag of cash?
钱在这事上不管用了，提诺
Money ain't gonna do it, Tino.
兄弟，我之前说过，他们派到芝加哥的那个人
Guy I mentioned before... The one they sent to Chicago...
他被雇佣的当天就消失了
Well, soon as he gets hired, he goes dark.
想取消这个任务不太可能了
There's no way of canceling the job.
很抱歉，提诺
I'm sorry, Tino.
我知道你想保护你的儿子
I know you want to protect your kid,
但是这帮人可真不是好惹的
but these guys...they don't play nice.
好吧，谢谢你，艾尔，我知道了
All right, thanks, Al.Message received.
他帮不上忙对吧？
He couldn't do anything, could he?
听着，这还不算完，孩子
Look, it's not over, kid.
我得赶紧离开这儿。坐下，别紧张
I got to get out of here.Sit down and relax.
你说你解决不了这个事
You said you could fix this.
我会解决的
And I will.
你就会吓唬人
You're a bully
以吓唬人为生
who scares people for a living.
听着，我把事情搞砸了，我觉得你能帮我
Look, I screwed up,and I thought you could help me,
但是这事太可怕了
but this is insane.
你没好好想想
You're not thinking straight.
我想了，现在他们都知道我是你儿子，他们肯定能找到我
Yeah, I am. Now they know I'm your son, they can find me.
我在亚伯塔（加拿大北部城市）有个朋友，我可以去找他
I got a buddy in Alberta I can stay with.
我走了
I'm out of here.
你怎么就知道你在加拿大就安全了呢？
What do you think...You're gonna be safe in Canada?
甭管你去哪他们都能找到你
They're gonna find you anywhere you go!
那又怎样，我就一直被软禁在这
So, what... I'm just supposed to stick around here
看着你跟我这儿演爸爸？
and let you play dad until then?
我不干
I don't think so.
你胸前戴的这个勋章
This medal that you're wearing on your chest...
告诉我这是怎了来的
Tell me about it.
这是我妈给我的
It was my mother's.
这是我曾祖父给她的
She got it from her grandfather.
不是，卢克，她没跟你说实话
No, Luke, she didn't.
这是我爷爷留给我的勋章
That medal belonged to my grandfather,
是我把它送给你妈妈的
and I gave it to your mother,
她不会无缘无故把这个勋章传给你
and she wouldn't have passed it on to you
除非她觉得
unless she thought there was something right
送给她勋章的这个人值得依靠
about the man who gave it to her.
不对，你胡说，她知道你是什么样的人
No. That's a lie. She knew what you were.
听着，事情没你想得那么简单
Look, it's not that easy.
我的意思是，
I mean, who I am...
到了我该对这个家承担责任的时候了
it may have been a liability back then.
现在，我要保护你
But now who I am is gonna save your life.
嘿，马斯蓝夫人怎么样了？
Hey.How's Mr. Maslan?
不太好
Not good.
EP检查什么也没查出来
E.P. studies were a bust.
我就不明白了
I can't figure this out.
其他化验结果怎么样？不怎么样
- What about the other tests?- Inconclusive.
他的回波搏动没有不正常反应
No structural abnormalities on his echo...
冠状动脉CT正常。电解检查呢？
- Normal coronary C.T.- Electrolytes?
钙，钾，镁，磷酸盐……
Calcium, potassium,magnesium, phos...
都正常
All normal.
要不试试换一种抗心律失常检查？
What about trying a different class of antiarrhythmic?
都试过了
All maxed out.
你说我会不会是第一个让病人死两次的
Do you realize I'm gonna be the first resident
住院医呢？
to have a patient die on me twice?
出事了！
Something's wrong!
点滴增压，可能是循环紊乱
Pressure's dropping.Looks like electrical alternans.
超声波
Ultrasound.
操
Damn it.
心肺复苏术肯定导致了心脏内膜出血
The CPR must have caused bleeding into the pericardium.
我需要18号针和一个大注射器
I need an 18-gauge needle and a large syringe.
我不明白
I don't understand.
我需要把斯图尔特心脏周围的血液抽出来
We need to drain the fluid from around Stuart's heart.
你确定吗？你们干得每一件事都只会让他变得更糟
Are you sure? Everything you've done has just made him worse.
抱歉，这是为了治疗并发症
I'm sorry for the complications,
但是我们必须把血吸出来
but we have to remove the blood
不然他的心脏就会停止跳动
or his heart will stop beating.
加油啊
You got it.
加油，斯图尔特，不要死
Come on, Stuart.Stay alive.
吉尔，好久不见，最近忙什么呢？
Gio, long time no see.Where you been?
啊，你知道，艾迪
Ah, you know, Eddie...
努力工作，确保生意运转
working hard,trying to keep the lights on.
你父亲的膝盖怎样了？
How's your dad's knee?
哦，很好，谢谢关心
Oh, it's good. It's good, thanks.
你知道，他说他的腿抽起来疼得要命
You know, he says it, uh,throbs like hell,
不过他最近报了个水疗班，已经好多了
but he's doing these aquatic classes and that's helping.
哦
Oh.
他最近在跟一帮老太太鬼魂
He's hanging out with a bunch of old broads...
那才是最有效的治疗
That's really what's helping.
哦，不好意思，艾迪，接个电话
Oh. Well, I'm sorry, Eddie.One second.
有事您吩咐，康老
What's up, Constantine?
没有
No.
不是，你儿子让我出来买点东西
No, your... your kid sent me to get some stuff
骑士旅馆没有电话
'cause they don't have any cable at the Esquire Motel.
杂志之类的
Like skin mags and stuff.
好的，我知道了
All right, I got it.
我知道了，一小时之内回去
I got it.I'll be back in an hour.
什么事啊？
What's that about? Ohh.
知道么，我突然之间就变成了一个
You know, it's like,all of a sudden,
傻逼保姆了
I'm a freaking babysitter.
他已经完全醒了，别问了
He's all wound up.Don't ask.
我要一个这个，好吗
I'm gonna take this.Okay.
我再来份报纸
Yeah, I'll take...I'll take a Trib, too.
好的
All right.
给你钱，别找了
There you go, Eddie.Keep the change.
回见了
Good to see you.
谢谢
Thanks.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
我有个拉撒路综合征病人
I had an emergency with a Lazarus Syndrome patient.
他怎么样？不怎么样
- Is he okay? - Barely.
奥利维亚正为此抓狂呢
Olivia's really beating herself up over it.
还有一个事
In other news...
看看这个，克洛伊的扫描结果出来了
Check this out.Chloe's scans came in.
肾脏瘤？
It's a kidney tumor?
确实是个肿瘤，不过不在她的肾脏上
It's definitely a tumor,but it is not on her kidney.
在她的前列腺上
It's in her prostate.
你这是什么意思？
What are you talking about?
她曾经是个……男人
She was born... a he.
前列腺
Seminal vesicles,
输精管双方向结扎
bilateral ligation of the vas deferens.
她是个变性人
She's a transgender female.
这就是为什么她会做了那么多整容手术
That explains the multiple cosmetic surgeries.
这就是为什么她不愿意看医生
And why she didn't want to see a doctor.
但就算她曾经是个男的，我还是不明白
But even if she was a man,I would have missed it.
我是说，她那么年轻，怎么会得前列腺肿瘤呢
I mean, she's way too young for prostate cancer.
因为这种手术之后
Well, not if she's taking estrogen
都得打大量的雌性激素
as part of her post-op protocol.
我定了间手术室
Well, I booked an O.R.
从她的出血速度来看
At the rate she's bleeding,
这个肿瘤的生长速度很快
this tumor's got to come out of her fast.
好吧，我去跟她谈谈
All right, I'll go talk to her.
好的
Okay.
嘿
Hey.
隔着绷带我看不见，我的胸部看上去怎么样？
I can't tell under the bandages.How do they look?
非常的好
They're gonna be great.
艾尔在哪？
Is, uh, Al around?
他去买吃的了，要我给他打电话吗？
He went to get food.Do you want me to call him?
不，不，不用了
No. No, that's okay.
哦
Um...
克洛伊，
Chloe.Mm-hmm.
你的化验结果出来了
Your C.T. came back,
结果上说你的前列腺上，
and it looks like you have cancer...
长了个肿瘤
In your prostate.
不会吧
That's not possible.
不幸的是，会的
Unfortunately, it is.
这就是你尿血的原因
It explains why you're peeing blood.
我是个女人
I'm a woman.
对，你是
Yeah, you are.
但是从医学的角度上来说，你曾经是个男人
But at one point, physically,you were a man.
你的检查结果显示出你的男性性征
Your C.T. showed remnants of your male reproductive tract,
包括你的前列腺
including your prostate...
长了个肿瘤
With a tumor.
我还以为我都把那部分切除了呢
I thought I got rid of that part of me.
它现在又来伤害我
And now here it is...Hurting me all over again.
我想你不能永远保守这个秘密了吧？
I guess you can't keep a secret forever, huh?
是啊
I guess not.
我们会让你度过这个难关的，好吗？
Look, we're gonna get you through this, okay?
这很重要
It is serious.
在手术和化疗之后，你就没事了
But with surgery and chemo,you're gonna do great.
不，你不明白
No,you don't understand.
我跟你说了这是个秘密
I told you it was a secret.
艾尔不知道这事
Al doesn't know.
亲爱的，你的癌症已经到了非常严重的程度
Sweetie,your cancer's pretty advanced.
我们得给你做手术
We got to get you into surgery.
怎么做？
How?
我意思是，如果艾尔知道了
I mean, if Al finds out...
咱俩就死定了
He'll kill us both.
嘿
Hey.
哦，手术很成功
So, the, uh, surgery went well.
你感觉怎么样？
How you feeling?
有点晕
A little out of it.
两个手术，一个接着一个的
Two surgeries,one on top of the other...
晕是正常的
What do you expect?
她怎么样？
How'd she do?
我们把她腹部的肿瘤完全去除了
Well, we were able to completely remove the abdominal tumor.
太好了，谢谢你
That's great news. Thank you.
你感觉怎么样？
How you doing, honey?
挺好的
Good.
但是，哦，我们发现了一个意外的并发症
But, uh, we ran into an unexpected complication.
手术的时候
When we got in there,
我们发现肿瘤扩散到了克洛伊的子宫里
we saw that, uh, the tumor had invaded Chloe's uterus...
所以我们必须把子宫切除
So we had to remove it.
那，你的意思是
So, you mean...
我们不能要孩子了？
I can't have kids?
很抱歉
I'm so sorry.
没事，亲爱的
It's okay, honey.
只要你能好起来就是最重要的
As long as you're healthy,that's all that matters.
我们要是哪天想要孩子了
We decide we want to have kids one day,
咱就领养一个，好吗？
we can just adopt, right?
德芙琳大夫，你怎么看？
What do you say,Dr. Devlin?
我看没问题
Definitely.
行了，你们俩单独待会吧
All right,I'll leave you two alone.
谢谢你为我做的这一切
Thank you...for everything.
你看他呀
Look at him.
他喘气儿都费劲了
He's barely breathing.
不幸的是，
Unfortunately, the procedure
这个治疗方法让他心率失常
seems to have complicated the arrhythmia.
这么说是你们把他治坏了
So you made him worse again.
贝瑟尼，亲爱的，别这么说
Bethany, baby, stop.Stop.
我需要你
I need you.
孩子需要你
He needs you.
我看见
I see...
圣光
Lights...
就像人们说的那样（临死前看见一道光）
Like people talk about.
别介
No.
什么样的光？马斯蓝先生？
What kind of light,Mr. Maslan?
光环
Halos...
金色的光环
Golden halos.
把检眼镜拿来
Get the ophthalmoscope.
这是怎回事？
What is it?
黄色光环可能是中毒的征兆
Uh, yellow halos may be a sign of toxicity.
你是说他老做噩梦吗？
You said he'd been having nightmares?
对，好几个礼拜了
Yeah, the past couple of weeks.
眼底正常
Fundi are normal.
我知道你说你们要采取自然生育
I know you said you were having a natural pregnancy,
但是斯图尔特感冒的时候有没有吃过什么草药之类的？
but did Stuart take anything herbal for his cold?
我只给他吃过止咳剂
Just a cough suppressant I got him.
我还带着呢
I think I have it.
毛地黄（又称“狐狸手套”一种强心剂草药）
Foxglove.
把地高辛解毒药拿来
Grab the digibind.
他吃了多少这种药？
How much has he been taking?
哦，我不知道，每次他咳嗽的时候就吃
Uh, I don't know...Whenever he coughs.
毛地黄是一种药效很猛的草药
Foxglove is an herbal version
学名叫“异羟洋地黄毒苷”
of a very potent Western medicine called "digoxin."
用量过大的话会导致严重的心律失常
An overdose can lead to a severe heart arrhythmia,
以及噩梦和幻觉
nightmares, and visual changes.
我只想用自然的方法生育孩子
I just wanted us to be healthy for the baby.
心率恢复正常了
The arrhythmia is resolving.
太好了
Yes, it is.
干得好，威尔科克斯大夫
Well done, Dr. wilcox.
我呼吸正常了
My breathing.
不，不，亲爱的
No. No, babe.
我已经好多了
It's better.
不，我说的不是那个
No, it's not that.
我觉得我的羊水好像破了
I think my water just broke.
啊？
What?
哦，护士！
Oh.Nurse!
通知产房，告诉他们我们需要一个床位
Uh, call up to L&D. Tell them we're gonna need a bed.
嘿，克洛伊，气色不错啊
Hey, Chloe.You're looking good.
细想想，我觉得还不是太糟糕，
I don't feel so bad...You know, considering.
你先回病房吧
I'll meet you back in the room.
我想单独跟德芙琳大夫谈谈
I just want to thank Dr. Devlin one-on-one.
很快的
Two minutes.
好吧
Okay.
克洛伊的癌症到底是怎么回事？
I need to know the truth about Chloe's cancer.
我不是说过了么
Well, like I said, she has...
别骗我，格蕾丝
Don't lie to me, Grace.
我了解她
I know about her.
我们已经好了有一阵子了
I've known about her for a while,
而且我始终还是爱她的
and I still love her.
好吧，这件事与我无关，
Okay, well, then, in that case,it's none of my business,
但是你为什么不告诉她你已经知道了呢？
but why don't you just tell her you know?
你说的对，这事跟你没关系
You're right.It's none of your business.
等我想好了之后，我会用我自己的方式告诉她的
I'll tell her when I'm ready and under my own terms.
我说明白了吗？
Do I make myself clear?
嗯
Yeah.
明白了
Of course.
你要是敢把这事告诉老康或者别人
If you ever tell Constantine or anyone else...
嘿，你别吓唬我行吗？
Hey, don't threaten me, okay?
我要是守不住秘密早就死了
If I couldn't keep a secret,I'd already be dead.
哥们，我想去吃中国菜
Buddy, I'm gonna go get some Chinese food.
用不用我给带回来点？
Do you want anything?
好吧
All right.
嘿，你回家啦？
Hey, you heading home?
是啊，哦，我还以为你都走了好长时间了呢
Yeah. Uh, I thought you left hours ago.
哦，我忙着弄马斯蓝的出院报告呢
Oh, I stuck around for the Maslan delivery.
是个男孩，七磅两盎司（六斤五两）
Baby boy...7 pounds, 2 ounces.
母子平安
Mother, child, and Lazarus
爸爸也没事了
are all doing very well.
真不错
That's great.
我告诉奥利维亚这个消息
And I prescribed a cocktail for Olivia,
她这回可以放心了
who is very much relieved.
这一天过得真紧张
It's been quite a day.
可不是么
Yeah.
你本来觉得挺顺的事吧
Just when you think you've seen it all,
它偏偏就拐着弯儿地折腾你
here comes the curve ball.
是啊，生活就是充满惊喜的，对吧？
Well, life is full of surprises,isn't it?
可不
Well...
回见了，格蕾丝
Good night, Grace.
我跟你说，老康对付这种事绝对是大师
I'm telling you, Constantine played it like a chess master...
让我把藏身的地方暴露给艾迪·拉索
Had me drop the location right in front of Eddie Russo.
拉索，那个讨厌的家伙总是信口雌黄
Russo... that creep's always shooting his mouth off.
没错，一个小时之内
Exactly.Within an hour,
我就从我手下那得到消息
I get word from my guy at Tijuana grill...
这家伙已经行动了
Balt's on the move.
除了艾迪·拉索之外，走漏风声的另有其人
Eddie Russo isn't the only one with a big mouth.
你觉得杀一个诺加莱斯·卡特尔的手下
What do you think...it's a joke
是闹着玩的吗？
to kill a member of the Nogales cartel?
昨天我留了消息
I left the message 24 hours ago.
你能告诉他亚历山大先生和我
Could you tell him Mr. Alexander and I
有要紧的事跟他谈吗？
need to speak with him urgently?
对，嗯，谢谢你
That's right. Mm-hmm. Thank you.
诺加莱斯的律师，
The, uh, Nogales lawyer,
随时会给我们打电话，这孙子
yeah, is calling us back any minute, the son of a bitch.
我刚跟特拉帕尼说了
I just spoke to Trapani.
卡特尔同意休战
The cartel agreed to a truce
不过我还得约他见面说这事
until I can have a sit-down with them.
太好了，头儿。走着瞧吧
That's great, boss.We'll see.
我从车上把行李拿出来了，我走了
I got my stuff from the car.I'm gonna take off.
听着，孩子，如果你跟我呆在一起
Listen, kid, I'd feel much better about things
我会感到很安心的
if you came and stayed at the house with me.
我不想让你觉得我感激涕零的
I don't want to seem ungrateful.
跟你一块呆着让我觉得别扭
I'm just... not comfortable with that.
但还是感谢你帮我这一回
But thank you...for what you did.
你不会是要出城吧？
Look, you're not gonna leave town, are you?
不出，我找个旅馆住下
No, I'm gonna check into a hotel,
再跟这儿待几天
stick around a couple days.
无论如何
Whatever you do,
住旅馆登记的时候别用真名
don't check into the hotel under your own name.
用现金结账
You pay in cash,
别让我之外的任何人进你的房间
and don't let anybody in the room till you hear from me.
好，我知道了
Yeah. I got it.
很高兴你能在这儿多待几天，卢克
I'm glad you're gonna stick around, Luke.
知道么，
You know, it gives us a chance
这也许是我们相互了解的好机会
to maybe get to know each other.
是啊
Sure.
我想见见格蕾丝
Look, I want to meet Grace.
我妈临死之前跟我提过她
Yeah, my mom told me about her before she died.
我觉得是时候我们见见面了
I think it's time we met.
我明白
I understand.
听着，这事我来安排
Listen to me...I'm gonna handle this,
但是你得跟我保证
but I want you to promise me
你一定要低调行事
you're gonna keep your head down.
加着小心
Be very careful.
行，我知道了
Okay. I will.
巴闭，把车钥匙给我
Give me the keys to the car, Bobby.
头儿，要不我开？
Boss, you want me to drive?
不行，这回我开吧
No, not this time.
我得自己处理这件事
It's something I got to do alone.
提诺，你这是干吗去呀？
Tino, what are you doing?
我去找德芙琳
I'm going to the Devlins'.
有件事我都拖了好久了，这回得把它办喽
It's something I should have taken care of a long time ago.
是的，是的，布克曼先生，很高兴你能给我打电话
Yes. Yes, Mr. Buchman,good to hear from you.
给你打电话是关于你的当事人诺加莱斯
I, uh, called regarding a business misunderstanding
在生意上的误会
with your clients from Nogales.
是，哦，我知道帕拉特尼已经跟你说过了
Yes, uh, I know Al Trapani has already reached out,
但是我们想直接……
but we would like to go on record direc...
你肯定吗？
You're certain about that?
我回头再打给你吧，谢谢你
I need to call you back, sir.Thank you.
接电话啊
Answer, answer.
提诺，诺加莱斯的律师回复了
Tino, the Nogales lawyer called back.
咱们有麻烦了
We have a problem.
特拉帕尼骗了咱们，卡特尔根本就没想休战
Trapani lied about the cartel.There is no truce.
特拉帕尼根本就没把你要偿还卢克的债务这个事跟他们说
Trapani never even passed on your offer to pay Luke's debt.
如果他们知道你没实现打招呼
If they find out you killed their man
就杀了他们的手下，这事很快就会升级
without trying to negotiate,this is going to get ugly fast.
提诺，赶紧给我回电话
Tino, call me as soon as you can.
哦，嘿
Oh. Hey.
我还说呢，谁进来了
I thought I heard someone come in.
你怎么样？还好
- How you doing?- Good.
我已经吃过了，要不我去给你热点儿剩菜？
I already ate, but I can heat you up some leftovers.
那太好了，谢谢你
Yeah, that sounds nice.Thank you.
我想赶紧去洗个澡
I'm just gonna take a shower real quick.
好的，你没事吧？
Okay. You okay?
没事啊，我挺好的
Yeah, I'm fine.
好吧，爱你啊
Okay. Love you.
我也爱你
I love you, too.
瑞是在盯梢呢
Is Ray watching out there,
还是坐那吃蛋糕呢？
or is he just sitting there,picking through pastries?
他一边盯梢一边吃蛋糕
He's watching.He's eating the pastries, too.
看这上写着，这姑娘采访的时候说
Look at this. This broad lies in the interview...
她的胸部不是隆的
Says those are real.
你还买这种玩意看呐？
You paid money for this thing?
你在网上都能免费看这些姑娘的裸体
You can go online and see these broads naked for nothing.
巴闭，这叫返璞归真
Bobby, there's something to be said about old-school.
嘿，你们俩谁知道老康的电话本放哪了？
Hey, did one of you two move Constantine's phone book?
哦，在菜单旁边
Uh, yeah, it's with the orders.
我跟他说过这种东西不能乱放
Did I not tell him to keep it closed?
可不么
You did.
康斯坦丁在哪？
Where's Constantine?
去你妈的
Go to hell.
他在哪？
Where is he?
我不知道
I don't know.
啊！
Ohh!
他在哪？
Where is he?
他-在-哪？
Where... is... he?
康斯坦丁
Constantine.
你这时候来干吗？
What's the occasion?
我们得告诉格蕾丝，丹尼
We got to tell Grace, Dannie.
告诉她什么呀？
Tell Grace what?
我们必须在她自己知道之前
We've got to tell her everything
把真相全都告诉她
before she finds out on her own.
妈？
Mom?
妈
Mom.
救命啊！
Help!
来人呐！
Somebody, help!
救命啊！
Help!!
==Thinks for watching! Chinese subtitle translate by @godort ==